### **Pavel Kuznetsov**

Android Developer Kyiv, Ukraine

Email / Skype: pavel.kuznetsov.5x@gmail.com

LinkedIn: <a href="http://www.linkedin.com/in/pavel-kuznetsov-abc">http://www.linkedin.com/in/pavel-kuznetsov-abc</a>

**Github:** <a href="https://github.com/pavel-kuznetsov-5x">https://github.com/pavel-kuznetsov-5x</a>

# **Summary**

I am a software engineer with 3+ years of experience in creating Android applications. I aspire to create maintainable, clean and robust code that is easy to change and reuse.

To efficiently communicate with other team members and understand higher-level problems, I always try to expand my knowledge in related areas, e.g. backend development, UI / UX, product management etc.

I also have experience in team management, gathering requirements from clients and product owners, creating documentation and interviewing developers.

#### **Skills**

#### **Android**

Android SDK, Java, Kotlin, RxJava, Retrofit, Dagger 2, Gradle

Clean Architecture, MVP, MVVM

Camera2, Custom Views

Jetpack Navigation, Room, DbFlow, FCM, Firebase Storage

Espresso

#### Other

Flutter, Python, Django

SQL, Neo4J

Team Management, Scrum, Jira

## **Education**

**NTUU** "Kyiv Polytechnic Institute"

**Computer Science** 

Bachelor's degree

2012 - 2016

## Languages

**English** – B2 (Upper-intermediate)

Russian, Ukrainian - Native

# **Experience**

### Freelance

Android Developer

Aug 2020 - now

• Likari24

### Selenium.com.ua

Android Developer

Jan 2020 - Apr 2020 (project closed due to COVID-19)

• App for face tracking of retail staff (to monitor working hours)

#### 920 Solutions

Android Developer

Mar 2019 - Jan 2020

- Space Digital Banking
- Participated in designing app architecture (for a complex multi-module app)
- Created workflow conventions for the team

# **EvoPlay**

Android Developer

Oct 2017 - May 2018

NDA

#### Tseh 2.0

Android Developer

May 2015 - May 2017

- Marketing app for providing branded goods to users in exchange for their selfies with corresponding goods or with branded photo overlay
- Healthcare app to notify users to take medications on time
- Gathering and documenting requirements
- Team management

## Tseh 2.0

Project Manager / Team Coordinator

Mar 2015 - May 2015

### i2i

Project Manager / Team Coordinator

Dec 2014 - Mar 2015

# **Freelance**

Android Developer

Various projects (freelance or on a part-time basis)

May 2017 - July 2019

- Chesno project AdBusters, app + backend
- ARVI project BeLike
- Tallium, inc. project FanLeague
- Bladeware project Perrzle
- Tseh 2.0 project Collider, backend